applelinks.com 2002-12-05

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for applelinks

**Applelinks** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Applelinks.com](http://www.applelinks.com/) and all the sites owned and operated by Coming Full Circle, Inc. 

#### Information Automatically Logged (Traffic Data)

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic traffic information. 

Traffic Data records the visitor's domain name or IP address of the ISP from which the user is logged on. We use software to keep track of traffic to our sites and derive such information as the location from which the traffic originates and which particular pages are being viewed and for how long. We may share information about visitors and traffic results with advertisers, for example, the number of visitors to our pages.  
**(Summary: Our Web Server collects the IP address of your ISP and lets us know how much traffic our site is generating. The information we share with our advertisers is not your individual information, but a general analysis of our web site's traffic ).**

#### Cookies

_Definition of a Cookie  
Data created by a Web server that is stored on a user's computer. It provides a way for the Web site to keep track of a user's patterns and preferences and, with the cooperation of the Web browser, to store them on the user's own hard disk._

_The cookies contain a range of URLs (addresses) for which they are valid. When the browser encounters those URLs again, it sends those specific cookies to the Web server. For example, if a user's ID were stored as a cookie, it would save that person from typing in the same information all over again when accessing that service for the second and subsequent time._

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart User ID, to limit voting to keep counts accurate, and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Sometimes we use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Applelinks cookies. 

We **DO NOT** use cookies to view sites you visit other than our own, to assess your "viewing habits." 

**(summary: Cookies are used to make the reader's experience more enjoyable, so they do not have to enter the same information over and over again.)**

#### Registration Forms, Surveys, Contests

Contact information from the registration forms is used to inform you about our company, and to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the [choice/opt-out section.](http://search.applelinks.com/register/optout.lasso)

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

**(summary: Registration requires that you provide some personal information. The Demographic data that is collected is used as a collective percentage from all our readers. For example: 40% Female and 60% Male, not John Doe who lives in Michigan makes 50,000 and drives a Ford)**

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **** Applelinks.com and all the sites owned and operated by Coming Full Circle, Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
